[
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In sharded clusters, delayed members have limited utility when the ____ is enabled.",
      "correct_answer": "Balancer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Collector",
        "Emitter",
        "Handler"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Subjective",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What is Hadoop MapReduce?",
      "correct_answer": "Done",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Skip"
      ]
    },
    {
     "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a valid Hadoop config file?",
      "correct_answer": "hadoop-site.xml",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "mapred-site.xml",
        "core-site.xml",
        "Masters"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which of the following database command is used for mapreduce function?",
      "correct_answer": "mapReduce",
      "incorrect_answers": ["mapperRed", "redmap", "None"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "MongoDB applies the _____ phase to each input document in mapreduce.",
      "correct_answer": "map",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "reduce",
        "mapper",
        "list"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "MongoDB applies the _________ phase, which collects and condenses the aggregated data.",
      "correct_answer": "reduce",
      "incorrect_answers": ["map", "connect", "mapper"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Map-reduce uses custom __________ functions to perform the map and reduce operations.",
      "correct_answer": "Java",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Javascript", "JSON", "JQuery"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Delayed members apply operations from the _______ on a delay.",
      "correct_answer": " oplog",
      "incorrect_answers": ["log", "mlog", "logs"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following databases employ fuzzy logic to draw inferences from imprecise data.",
      "correct_answer": "probabilistic database",
      "incorrect_answers": ["spatial database","Real-time database","temporal database"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is Hive used as?",
      "correct_answer": "All",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hadoop query engine",
        "MapReduce wrapper",
        "Hadoop SQL interface"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Nosql-Objective",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the default HDFS replication factor?",
      "correct_answer": "3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1",
        "4",
        "2"
      ]
    }
  ]
  